Guide to the Jack Metcalf Papers 1973-2001
Western Washington University, Center for Pacific Northwest Studies
- Congressional Career, 1984-2001; 1995-2000; Series II
  - District Office Files, 1995-2000; Subseries 2
    - Legislative issues
      - Olympic Pipeline Explosion, 1999 (Box-folder 29/14)
      - Pacific Northwest Trails Association, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 29/15)
      - Planet CPR’s Grate Mate Campaign, 1999 (Box-folder 29/16)
      - Postmasters Convention, Bellingham, 2000 (Box-folder 29/17)
      - Salmon Fishery Buy Back Program, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 29/18)
      - Salmon Fishing Closure 7A/ Letter to Bern Shanks, 1997 (Box-folder 29/19)
      - SeaTac Airport 3rd Runway Issue (SCRAP), 1996 (Box-folder 29/20)
      - Semiahmoo Spit Sewage Treatment Facility Issue, 2000 (Box-folder 29/21)
      - Sen.Gorton’s Pacific Northwest Salmon Hearing, 1999 April 7 (Box-folder 29/22)
      - Snohomish/Arlington Trail Association, 2000 (Box-folder 29/23)
      - Snohomish/State Route 20/ Marches Pt. Road, 1996 (Box-folder 29/24)
      - Swinomish Leasehold (HR 4260), 1996-1998 (Box-folder 29/25)
      - Swinomish Water Rights, 1995 (Box-folder 29/26)
      - Taipai Cultural Office in Seattle, 2000 (Box-folder 29/27)
      - U.S. Department of Justice Wireless Management Center, 2000 (Box-folder 29/28)
      - U.S. Federal Highway 2 Safety Coalition, 1997 (Box-folder 29/29)
      - U.S. Military
        - Borsellino Case, 1999 (Box-folder 29/30)
        - EA6B Crash, 1996 (Box-folder 29/31)
        - EA6B Prowler, 2000 (Box-folder 29/32)
        - Ebey’s Landing National Historical Reserve, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 29/33)
        - HMT Rohna incident (Metcalf resolution), 2000 (Box-folder 29/34)
        - Homeless Veterans Symposium Packet, 1998 (Box-folder 29/35)
        - Juvenile Detention, 1998 (Box-folder 29/36)
        - Madigan Hospital, Fort Lewis, 1998 (Box-folder 29/37)
        - Metcalf Tribute to Jim Pace, U.S. Veteran, 1997 (Box-folder 29/38)
        - Naval Station, Everett, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 29/39)
        - Navy Reserve Issues (NAS Whidbey), 1996 (Box-folder 29/40)
        - Search and Rescue Unit (Whidbey Island), 1996 (Box-folder 29/41)
        - U.S. Veterans – Stand Down, 1998 (Box-folder 29/42)
        - USS Abraham Lincoln Home Base and Transportation, 1997 (Box-folder 29/43)
        - Veterans Town Meeting, 1997 (Box-folder 29/44)
        - Whidbey Island Base Closure, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 29/45)
      - Washington State Department of Transportation- Pacific Northwest Rail Corridor, 1995 (Box-folder 29/46)
      - Whatcom County Council of Governments - Scenic Byways, 2000 (Box-folder 29/47)
      - Whatcom County Land Trust, 1998 (Box-folder 29/48)
    - Awards, 1995-2000
      - Certificates and Photos, 1995-2000 (Box-folder 30/1)
      - Plaques
        - POW – MIA Flag Ceremony (Mount Vernon Post Office), 1998 (Box-folder 30/2)
        - Susan B. Anthony List (diligence to protect the unborn), 1999 (Box-folder 30/3)
        - Naval Criminal Investigative Service Puget Sound- Top Gun Award, undated (Box-folder 30/4)